<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Assignment3</string>
    <string name="one_name">Pikachu</string>
    <string name="sec_name">Charmamder</string>
    <string name="third_name">Bulbasaur</string>
    <string name="fourth_name">Squirtle</string>
    <string name="fifth_name">Raichu</string>
    <string name="sixth_name">Charizard</string>
    <string name="seventh_name">Blastoise</string>
    <string name="eight_name">Venusaur</string>
    <string name="ome_type">Electric</string>
    <string name="two_type">Fire</string>
    <string name="three_type">Grass</string>
    <string name="four_type">Water</string>
    <string name="five_type">Electric</string>
    <string name="six_type">Fire</string>
    <string name="seven_type">Water</string>
    <string name="eight_type">Grass</string>
    <string name="one_height">0.4 m</string>
    <string name="two_height">0.6 m</string>
    <string name="three_height">0.7 m</string>
    <string name="four_height">0.5 m</string>
    <string name="five_height">0.8 m</string>
    <string name="six_height">1.7 m</string>
    <string name="seven_height">1.6 m</string>
    <string name="eight_height">2.0 m</string>
    <string name="one_weight">13.2 lbs</string>
    <string name="two_weight">18.7 lbs</string>
    <string name="three_weight">15.2 lbs</string>
    <string name="four_weight">19.8 lbs</string>
    <string name="five_weight">66.1 lbs</string>
    <string name="six_weight">199.5 lbs</string>
    <string name="seven_weight">188.5 lbs</string>
    <string name="eight_weight">220.5 lbs</string>
    <string name="one_detail">Pikachu is a short, chubby rodent Pokémon. It is covered in yellow fur with two horizontal brown stripes on its back. It has a small mouth, long, pointed ears with black tips, brown eyes, and the two red circles on its cheeks contain pouches for electricity storage. It has short forearms with five fingers on each paw, and its feet each have three toes. At the base of its lightning bolt-shaped tail is a patch of brown fur. A female will have a V-shaped notch at the end of its tail, which looks like the top of a heart. It is classified as a quadruped, but it has been known to stand and walk on its hind legs. </string>
    <string name="two_detail">Charmander is a bipedal, reptilian Pokémon with a primarily orange body. Its underside from the chest down and its walking pads are cream-colored. It has two small fangs visible in its upper jaw and two smaller fangs in its lower jaw.Charmander has blue eyes. Its arms and legs are short with four fingers and three clawed toes. </string>
    <string name="three_detail">Bulbasaur is a small, quadruped Pokémon that has turquoise skin with darker teal patches. It has red eyes with white pupils and scleras. It also has pointed, ear-like structures on top of its head. Its snout is short and blunt, and it has a wide mouth. A pair of small, pointed teeth are visible in the upper jaw when its mouth is open. Each of its thick legs ends with three sharp claws.</string>
    <string name="four_detail">Squirtle is a small Pokémon that resembles a light blue turtle. While it typically walks on its two short legs, it has been shown to run on all fours in Super Smash Bros. Brawl. It has large eyes and a slightly hooked upper lip. Each of its hands and feet has three pointed digits. The end of its long tail curls inward.</string>
    <string name="five_detail">Raichu is a bipedal, rodent-like Pokémon. Raichu is covered in dark orange fur with a white belly. Its bifurcated ears are brown on the outside, yellow on the insides, and end in a distinctive curl. There are circular yellow markings on its cheek where its electric sacs are, and it has a triangular, dark brown nose. Its arms and feet have patches of brown fur at the end, and the soles of its big feet are tan with a circular orange pad. On its back are two horizontal brown stripes. </string>
    <string name="six_detail">Charizard is a draconic, bipedal Pokémon. It is primarily orange with a cream underside from the chest to the tip of its tail, which burns with a sizable flame. Charizard has a long neck, small blue eyes, raised nostrils, and two horn-like structures protruding from the back of its rectangular head. There are two fangs visible in the upper jaw when its mouth is closed. </string>
    <string name="seven_detail">Blastoise is a large, bipedal turtle-like Pokémon. Its body is blue and is mostly hidden by its tough, brown shell. This shell has a pale yellow underside and a white ridge encircling its arms and separating the upper and lower halves. Two powerful water cannons reside in the top sides of its shell. These cannons can be extended or withdrawn and can be used to assist in high-speed charges.</string>
    <string name="eight_detail">Venusaur is a squat, quadruped Pokémon with bumpy, blue-green skin. It has small, circular red eyes, a short, blunt snout, and a wide mouth with two pointed teeth in the upper jaw and four in the lower jaw. On top of its head are small, pointed ears with reddish pink insides. It has three clawed toes on each foot. The bud on its back has bloomed in a large pink, white-spotted flower. The flower is supported by a thick, brown trunk surrounded by green fronds.</string>
</resources>
